Bridge Line Historical Society; Collection mss129
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Maps, Blueprints, and Drawings, 1870-2004; 2; 613 items
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line; Binghamton to Albany, Station 131+19 to Station 184+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 173)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001234
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line; Binghamton to Albany, Station 184+00 to Station 237+37 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 182)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001235
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line; Binghamton to Albany, Station 237+37 to Station 289+03.7 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 184)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001236
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Mechanicville Branch; Glenville Junction to Coons, Station 105+60 to Station 158+40 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 179)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001183
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Mechanicville Branch; Glenville Junction to Coons, Station 158+40 to Station 211+20 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 198)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001184
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Mechanicville Branch; Glenville Junction to Coons, Station 264+00 to Station 316+80 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 185)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001186
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Schenectady Branch, Delanson to Schenectady, Station 0+00 to Station 43+00 and Station 0+00 to Station 52+80 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 533)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001266
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Schenectady Branch; Delanson to Schenectady and Mechanicville Branch; Glenville Junction to Coons (14 sheets) (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 183)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Numbers: BLA001219 to BLA001232
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division, Mechanicville Branch, Glenville Junction to Coons; Station 211+20 to 264+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 142)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001185
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division, Mechanicville Branch, Glenville Junction to Coons; Station 316+80 to 369+60 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 132)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001187
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division, Schenectady Branch, Delanson to Schenectady; Station 666+55 to Station 708+77 (also Station 675+60 to Station 695+78.55 Southbound) (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 156)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001238
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division, Station 1923+49.4 to Station 1976+46.3 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 437)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001163
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Schenectady Branch, Delanson to Schenectady, Station 43+00 to Station 99+00 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 504)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001352
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Ticonderoga Railroad, Station 0+00 to Station 30+97 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 188)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001255
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Unidentified Station Map, Undated (Map-tube 443)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001382
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation; Saratoga Division Main Line, Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 4063+60 to Station 4117+60, Undated (Map-tube 496)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001344
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation; Saratoga Division Main Line, Saratoga Springs to Lake Station, Station 4063+60 to Station 4117+60 (Reproduction of 1934 Map), Undated (Map-tube 520)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000931
  - Right of Way and Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station 1554+05 to Station 1607+17 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 429)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001162
  - Roof Plan of Shop #7 in Oneonta, NY, 1923 (Map-tube 239)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000480
  - Roof Trusses and Location and Capacity of Hoists Shop #7 in Oneonta, NY (Reproduction of 1957 Map), Undated (Map-tube 219)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000482
  - Saratoga County, Spier Falls Area: Conveyance of Property /Power Line Easement for Adirondack Power & Light, Former Hudson Valley Railroad Right of Way (Eight Sheets in Set), 1932 (Map-tube 101)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000079; Other Identification Number: 12-38753
  - Saratoga Division - Valuation Section #V8; Proposed Change of Line, North Albany to Green Island, 1944 (Map-tube 48)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000065
  - Saratoga Wye, Scale 50 ft. to inch; Working Drawing, Undated (Map-tube 14)
  - Saratoga, Old Map (Church Street to ...; Includes Rensselaer & Saratoga Freight House, 3-track Roundhouse, 45-foot Turntable, and Station), [1870] (Map-tube 2)
    Other Identification Number: 708-1619
  - Sketch of Area in [Austerlitz] NY?, Undated (Map-tube 89)
    Other Identification Number: 104-809
  - Sketch of Slow Flag, Undated (Map-tube 334)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001109
  - Standard Private Railroad Crossing Sign (Reproduction of 1910 Sign), Undated (Map-tube 9)
  - Station Maps-Lands: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Susquehanna Division Main Line, Binghamton to Albany, Station7462+00 to Station 7514+79.8 (Reproduction of 1916 Map), Undated (Map-tube 500)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001348
  - Street and Tracks South of State Street, Schenectady; Map #1, [Pre-1918] (Map-tube 7)
    Other Identification Number: 708-1492
  - Summary of Tracks: Sidney Tracks and Yard, 1882 (Map-tube 40)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000060; Other Identification Number: 527-4944
  - Susquehanna Division Signal Diagrams (14 sheets), 1970 (Map-tube 178)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001249
  - Table of Stringers Required for Various Clear Spans, Undated (Map-tube 280)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001123
  - Table of Train Stations, Undated (Map-tube 585)
  - Tax Map of Maiden Lane to Madison Avenue Albany, NY, Undated (Map-tube 57)
    Other Identification Number: 1966-34 1-A
  - Terminal Board Equipment: Six Way Relay Box Blueprint, Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - The Bridge Line to New England and Canada, 1823-1973 Poster, 2004 (Map-tube 20)
  - The Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division; Building to be Erected at Shelburne Harbor, VT (Reproduction of 1910 Map), Undated (Map-tube 196)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001244-BLA001245
  - The Delaware and Hudson Company: Champlain Division; Proposed Boiler House and Coal Trestle in Rouses Point, N.Y., Undated (Map-tube 197)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001237
  - The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Track and Signal Arrangement from Afton to Crescent, NY, 1963; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000926 and BLA000927
  - The Delaware and Hudson Railway Company: Force Account Work Site Plan and Profile for Proposed Locomotive Facility at East Binghamton Yard Conklin, N.Y. (6 sheets), 1983 (Map-tube 195)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001252
  - The Hall Signal Company: Clamp Shaft Bearing Blueprint (Reproduction of 1918 Map), Undated (Map-tube 588)
  - Town Map of Schoharie Junction, NY (Reproduction 1937), Undated (Map-tube 438)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000460; Other Identification Number: 21-359
  - Town of Champlain, County of Clinton: Public Service Case #4912, Delaware & Hudson RR Co., Elimination of Grade Crossings, Baker Crossing Near Cooperville (Eight Sheets), 1929 (Map-tube 116)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000072; Other Identification Number: 465-32851
  - Tracing from U.S. Government Map Showing by Red Border Lands Purchase by Hudson River Estates, Incorporated in the Town of Colonie, Albany County, NY, Undated (Map-tube 584)
  - Tracing of Map No. 6 of the Saratoga and Schenectady Rail Road, 1915 (Map-tube 404)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001367
  - Tracing of Maps of Saratoga and Schenectady Railroad (2 Sheets), 1915 (Map-tube 423)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001360
  - Tracings and [Nigarious] of Eastern Traffic Map [?], Undated (Map-tube 130)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000006
  - Track Changes in Schenevus, Undated (Map-tube 463)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000496
  - Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale; Station 1806+92.5 to Station 1859+58.9 (Reproduction of 1945 Map), Undated (Map-tube 154)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001195
  - Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Company; Pennsylvania Division Main Line, Green Ridge to Carbondale; Station 1806+92.5 to Station 1859+58.9 (Reproduction of 1945 Map), Annotated, Undated (Map-tube 523)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000875
  - Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Colonie Shops, General Layout (Reproduction of 1944 Map), Undated (Map-tube 522)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000928
  - Track Map: The Delaware and Hudson Railroad Corporation: Saratoga Division; Colonie Shops, General Layout (Reproduction of 1944 Map), Annotated, Undated (Map-tube 525)
  - Transfer Cradle for Yacht, Undated (Map-tube 416)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001358; Other Identification Number: 711-620
  - Transverse Views of Auxiliary Cab #1 End (Reproduction of 1905 Map), Undated (Map-tube 440)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000857
  - Troy & Albany Branch with Profile, Undated (Map-tube 4)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000027
  - Troy Union Railroad: Sketch of Tracks 3-30-08 (Reproduction of 1927 Map), Undated (Map-tube 61)
    Other Identification Number: 303-34475 and 5-435-B
  - Unidentifiable Blueprint of Quay Street [Albany?], Undated (Map-tube 86)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000084; Other Identification Number: 723-3094?
  - Unidentifiable Blueprint of Train Station Locations [?], Undated (Map-tube 256)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000546; Other Identification Number: BL-02-03-06-1
  - Unidentifiable Schematic of Train Station Skylights [?], Undated (Map-tube 410)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000481A-BLA000481B
  - Unidentified Map of Rail Yards, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000865
  - Unidentified Schematic of Train Car with Statistics, Map Number 567, Undated (Flat-file 3)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA001320
  - Unidentified Track and Land Arrangements (Four Sheets), Undated (Map-tube 581)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000860A-BLA000860D
  - Unidentified Track and Signal Map, Undated (Map-tube 575)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number:BLA000922
  - Unidentified Track and Signal Map for Wilkes-Barre Connecting, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000894
  - Unidentified Track and Signal Map North of Carbondale, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000887
  - Warranty Deed (two sheets) with Land Map for Wallace Baker Lot (Warrensburg Branch), Undated (Map-tube 96)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000088; Other Identification Number: 12-2725
  - Western Vermont Agricultural Society Grounds: Fairhaven, Undated (Map-tube 113)
    Other Identification Number: 708-1820
  - Wilkes-Barre Connecting Railroad Company: Track and Signal Arrangement in Hudson, PA, 1956 (Map-tube 553)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000893
  - Wilkes-Barre Connecting Railroad Company: Track, Signal and Telephone Arrangement Between Hudson and Carey Avenue, North End Buttonwood Yard (Reproduction of 1959 Map), Map Number 565, Undated (Flat-file 5)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000892
  - Working Alignment Drawing; Oneonta toward Binghamton (MP124 to apx MP95), Undated (Map-tube 43)
    Original Bridge Line Identification Number: BLA000068; Other Identification Number: 532-22721
- Newsletters, 1991-2020; 3; 3.0 cubic ft.
  This series is comprised of newsletters from the Bridge Line Historical Society known as the Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin.
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 1, Numbers 1-3, 1991 January-March; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 1, Numbers 4-6, 1991 April-June (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 1, Numbers 7-9, 1991 July-September (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 1, Numbers 10-12, 1991 October-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 2, Numbers 1-3, 1992 January-March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 2, Numbers 4-6, 1992 April-June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 2, Numbers 7-9, 1992 July-September (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 2, Numbers 10-12, 1992 October-December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 3, Numbers 1-3, 1993 January-March (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 3, Numbers 4-6, 1993 April-June (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 3, Numbers 7-9, 1993 July-September (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 3, Numbers 10-12, 1993 October-December (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 4, Numbers 1-3, 1994 January-March (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 4, Numbers 4-6, 1994 April-June (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 4, Numbers 7-9, 1994 July-September (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 4, Numbers 10-12, 1994 October-December (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 5, Numbers 1-3, 1995 January-March (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 5, Numbers 4-6, 1995 April-June (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 5, Numbers 7-9, 1995 July-September (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 5, Numbers 10-12, 1995 October-December (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 6, Numbers 1-3, 1996 January-March (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 6, Numbers 4-6, 1996 April-June (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 6, Numbers 7-9, 1996 July-September (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 6, Numbers 10-12, 1996 October-December (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 7, Numbers 1-3, 1997 January-March (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 7, Numbers 4-6, 1997 April-June (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 7, Numbers 7-9, 1997 July-September (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 7, Numbers 10-12, 1997 October-December (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 8, Numbers 1-3, 1998 January-March (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 8, Numbers 4-6, 1998 April-June (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 8, Numbers 7-9, 1998 July-September (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 8, Numbers 10-12, 1998 October-December (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 9, Numbers 1-3, 1999 January-March (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 9, Numbers 4-6, 1999 April-June (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 9, Numbers 7-9, 1999 July-September (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 9, Numbers 10-12, 1999 October-December (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 10, Numbers 1-3, 2000 January-March (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 10, Numbers 4-6, 2000 April-June (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 10, Numbers 7-9, 2000 July-September (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 10, Numbers 10-12, 2000 October-December (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 11, Numbers 1-3, 2001 January-March (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 11, Numbers 4-6, 2001 April-June (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 11, Numbers 7-9, 2001 July-September (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 11, Numbers 10-12, 2001 October-December (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 12, Numbers 1-3, 2002 January-March (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 12, Numbers 4-6, 2002 April-June (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 12, Numbers 7-9, 2002 July-September (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 12, Numbers 10-12, 2002 October-December (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 13, Numbers 1-3, 2003 January-March (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 13, Numbers 4-6, 2003 April-June (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 13, Numbers 7-9, 2003 July-September (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 13, Numbers 10-12, 2003 October-December (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 14, 1-3, 2004 January-March (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 14, 4-6, 2004 April-June (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 14, Numbers 7-9, 2004 July-September (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 14, Numbers 10-12, 2004 October-December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 15, Numbers 1-3, 2005 January-March (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 15, Numbers 4-6, 2005 April-June (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 15, Numbers 7-9, 2005 July-September (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 15, Numbers 10-12, 2005 October-December (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 16, Numbers 1-3, 2006 January-March (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 16, Numbers 4-6, 2006 April-June (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 16, Numbers 7-9, 2006 July-September (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 16, Number 10-12, 2006 October-December (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 17, Numbers 1-3, 2007 January-March (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 17, Number 4, 2007 April (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 17, Number 8, 2007 August (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 17, Number 12, 2007 December (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 18, Number 1, 2008 January (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 18, Numbers 4-6, 2008 April-June (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 18, Numbers 7-9, 2008 July-September (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 18, Number 11, 2008 November (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 22, Numbers 10-12, 2012 October-December (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 23, Number 2, 2013 February (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 23, Number 5, 2013 May (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 23, Number 6, 2013 June (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 23, Number 7, 2013 July (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 23, Number 8, 2013 August (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 23, Numbers 10-12, 2013 October-December (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 24, Numbers 1-3, 2014 January-March (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 24, Numbers 4-6, 2014 April-June (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 24, Numbers 7-9, 2014 July-September (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 24, Numbers 10-12, 2014 October-December (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 25, Numbers 1-3, 2015 January-March (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 25, Numbers 4-6, 2015 April-June (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 25, Numbers 7-9, 2015 July-September (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 25, Numbers 10-12, 2015 October-December (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 26, Numbers 1-3, 2016 January-March (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 26, Numbers 4-6, 2016 April-June (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 26, Numbers 7-9, 2016 July-September (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 26, Numbers 10-12, 2016 October-December (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 27, Numbers 1-3, 2017 January-March (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 27, Numbers 4-6, 2017 April-June (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 27, Numbers 7-9, 2017 July-September (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 27, Numbers 10-12, 2017 October-December (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 28, Numbers 1-3, 2018 January-March (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 28, Numbers 4-6, 2018 April-June (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 28, Numbers 7-9, 2018 July-September (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bridge Line Historical Society Bulletin Vol. 28, Numbers 10-12, 2018 October-December (Box 3, Folder 12)